[
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [11, 12, 13, 14, 15]?",
      "correctAnswer": "13",
      "options": [
        "12",
        "13",
        "14",
        "15"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [12, 13, 14, 15, 16]?",
      "correctAnswer": "14",
      "options": [
        "13",
        "14",
        "15",
        "16"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [13, 14, 15, 16, 17]?",
      "correctAnswer": "15",
      "options": [
        "14",
        "15",
        "16",
        "17"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [14, 15, 16, 17, 18]?",
      "correctAnswer": "16",
      "options": [
        "15",
        "16",
        "17",
        "18"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [15, 16, 17, 18, 19]?",
      "correctAnswer": "17",
      "options": [
        "16",
        "17",
        "18",
        "19"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [16, 17, 18, 19, 20]?",
      "correctAnswer": "18",
      "options": [
        "17",
        "18",
        "19",
        "20"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [17, 18, 19, 20, 21]?",
      "correctAnswer": "19",
      "options": [
        "18",
        "19",
        "20",
        "21"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [18, 19, 20, 21, 22]?",
      "correctAnswer": "20",
      "options": [
        "19",
        "20",
        "21",
        "22"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [19, 20, 21, 22, 23]?",
      "correctAnswer": "21",
      "options": [
        "20",
        "21",
        "22",
        "23"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 120]?",
      "correctAnswer": "23",
      "options": [
        "22",
        "23",
        "24",
        "25"
      ]
    }
]